fcpeuro.com 2015-09-11

# Privacy Policy | FCP Euro

FCP GROTON, LLC ("FCP Euro", 'FCP Import", "FCP Groton", "FCP Stores", "FCP") respects the privacy of every individual who visits this Web site (the "Site"). We have created this Privacy Statement to inform you of the information collection practices for this Site, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. Please carefully read this Privacy Statement and revisit it from time to time as it may periodically be revised. By using this Site, you indicate your understanding and acceptance of these terms. If you do not accept these terms, you may not use this Site.

* * *

### Personally Identifiable Information that We Collect

In general, you can visit this Site without identifying yourself or revealing any personally identifiable information. There are times, however, that you may choose to give us personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, or other information about yourself. For example, if you would like to place an order you will need to provide us with your e-mail address, billing and shipping addresses, and payment information. Another example would be if in response to employment opportunities at FCP, you e-mail your resume to us. We also provide you with the opportunity to e-mail us questions or comments about this Site and our company.

* * *

### Our Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information

We only use and store the personally identifiable information which is provided by you through this Site to help us improve our services to you, to provide you with the information you have requested, to respond to your questions or resume submission, and for other internal purposes. We may also enhance or merge personally identifiable information you provide with data obtained from others for the same purposes. FCP will not give or sell your personally identifiable information to any organization other than a direct affiliate or successor in interest to FCP for such organization's own use without your consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be shared with agents or contractors of FCP or other entities in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for FCP. FCP may also use your personally identifiable information for disclosures that are required by law.

* * *

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically

In some cases, we may collect information that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of internet browser or computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our Site or advertisement. FCP does not collect personally identifiable information automatically, but we may tie information collected automatically to your previously submitted personally identifiable information.

In addition, some pages on this Site may use "cookies" ?small files that the Site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages you visit, but the only personal information a cookie contains is information that you supply. Note that cookies cannot read data off of your hard drive. These files are used for site registration and customization the next time you visit us. Some parts of the Site may also use cookies to track your traffic patterns. We do this to help us understand the usefulness of our Site, the effectiveness of our navigational structure, and to develop enhancements to the Site for your convenience.

Any non-personally identifiable material, information, suggestions, ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, questions, comments or other communication you transmit or post to this Site in any manner is and will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary ("User Communications"). FCP, each of its affiliates and/or their designees may use any or all User Communications for any purpose whatsoever, including, without limitation, reproduction, transmission, disclosure, publication, broadcast, development, manufacturing and/or marketing in any manner whatsoever for any or all commercial or non-commercial purposes. FCP may, but is not obligated to, monitor or review any information you provide through this Web Site. FCP shall have no obligations to use, return, review, or respond to any requests, information, questions, material, comments, submissions or other communications through this Web Site. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this Site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, offensive, pornographic, or other material that would violate any law. FCP will have no liability related to the content of any such communications, whether or not arising under the laws of copyright, libel, privacy, obscenity, or otherwise.

* * *

### Changes to Information

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested or send us an email to info@fcpgroton.com.

* * *

### Links to Other Web Sites

From time to time, this Site may contain links to other Web sites. If you use these links, you will leave this Site. The privacy policy of such other Web sites govern the information collection and dissemination practices occurring on such Web sites. We encourage you to read and understand those Web sites' policies prior to using those Web sites. Neither FCP nor its affiliates are responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### NOTICE: CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 18 & THEIR PARENTS OR LEGAL GUARDIANS

* * *

Our site is intended for adults. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not send FCP any personal information. If you know of anyone under the age of 18 who has provided us with information, please contact us immediately and we will remove the information.

### Privacy Protection Policy

In accordance with applicable law, we take additional security measures in regards to our collection, storage, and disposal of Social Security numbers. First, we take what we believe to be reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers. Second, we limit access to Social Security numbers to only those persons with a legitimate business purpose. Third, we provide appropriate training to employees and prohibit the unlawful disclosure of Social Security numbers. Finally, we protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers by using data encryption and secure data storage procedures and destroying, erasing, or making unreadable Social Security numbers prior to disposal. These procedures are periodically reviewed to help maintain the confidentiality of Social Security numbers.

* * *

### Questions Concerning this Privacy Statement

Contact us with any questions regarding this privacy statement.

Contact Us
